phase2technology.com 2019-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Phase2

**(a)  ** **Information You Provide to Us**  

**Personal Information and Demographic Information.**   On the Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain categories of information such as: (1) personally identifiable information, which is information that identifies you personally, such as your first and last name, phone number, e-mail address, and home address (“ **Personal Information** ”); and (2) demographic information, such as information about your type of business, revenues, education level, job title, and occupation. (“ **Demographic Information** ”).  We may collect this information through various forms and in various places on the Service, including contact us forms or when you otherwise interact with the Service.  To the extent we combine Demographic Information with your Personal Information we collect directly from you on the Service, we will treat the combined data as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy.  

**(b) Information Collected or Stored As You Access and Use the Service**  

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us via our Service, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Service (“ **Usage Information** ”).  This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a “ **Device** ”) whenever you visit or interact with our Service.  To the extent we associate Usage Information with your Personal Information we collect directly from you on the Service, we will treat it as Personal Information.   

This Usage Information may include:

  * your IP address, UDID or other unique identifier (“ **Device Identifier** ”).  A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Service, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier;
  * your Device functionality (including browser, operating system, hardware, mobile network information);
  * the URL that referred you to our Service;
  * the areas within our Service that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences;
  * your Device location;
  * your Device characteristics; and
  * certain other Device data, including the time of day, among other information. 

**Tracking Technologies**.  We may use various methods and technologies to store or collect Usage Information (“ **Tracking Technologies** ”).  Tracking Technologies may set, change, alter or modify settings or configurations on your Device. A few of the Tracking Technologies include, without limitation, the following (and subsequent technology and methods later developed):  

**_Cookies_**.  A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Service.  A Flash cookie (or locally shared object) is a data file placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Device.  HTML5 cookies can be programmed through HTML5 local storage.  

**_Web Beacons_**.  Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “1x1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in our Service’s pages and messages.  Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a page or e-mail can act as a web beacon.  Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Service, to monitor how users navigate the Service, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.   

**_Embedded Scripts_**.  An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Service, such as the links you click on.  The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Service, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.    

**_Browser Fingerprinting_**.  Collection and analysis of information from your Device, such as, without limitation, your operating system, plug-ins, system fonts and other data, for purposes of identification.   

**_ETag, or Entity Tag_**.  A feature of the cache in browsers.  It is an opaque identifier assigned by a web server to a specific version of a resource found at a URL.  If the resource content at that URL ever changes, a new and different ETag is assigned.  Used in this manner ETags are a form of Device Identifier.  ETag tracking may generate unique tracking values even where the consumer blocks HTTP, Flash, and/or HTML5 cookies.   

**_Recognition Technologies._**   Technologies, including application of statistical probability to data sets, which attempt to recognize or make assumptions about users and devices (e.g., that a user of multiple devices in the same user).  

**Tracking Technologies Usage**.  We may use Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes, including:  

**_Strictly Necessary_**.  We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that we consider are strictly necessary to allow you to use and access our Service, including cookies required to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security or allow you to make use of certain functionality.   

**_Performance_** ‑ ** _Related_**.  We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are useful in order to assess the performance of the Service, including as part of our analytic practices or otherwise to improve the content, products or services offered through the Service.   

**_Functionality_** ‑ ** _Related_**.  We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are required to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing the Service, including identifying you when you sign‑in to our Service or keeping track of your specified preferences, including in terms of the presentation of content on our Service.   

**_Targeting_** ‑ ** _Related_**.  We may use Tracking Technologies to deliver content, including ads, relevant to your interests on our Service and third‑party sites based on how you interact with our advertisements or content.  This includes using Tracking Technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the content that has been delivered to you.  Further information on this, and your opt-out choices, is found in Section 5 below.  

**Third Party Tracking and Do Not Track**.  

There may be other Tracking Technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the Service.  Further, third parties may use Tracking Technologies in connection with our Service, which may include the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services.  We may not control those Tracking Technologies and we are not responsible for them.  However, you consent to potentially encountering third party Tracking Technologies in connection with use of our Service and accept that our statements under this Privacy Policy do not apply to the Tracking Technologies or practices of such third parties.  Also, various third parties are developing or have developed signals or other mechanisms for the expression of consumer choice regarding the collection of information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services (e.g., browser do not track signals).  Currently, we do not monitor or take any action with respect to these signals or other mechanisms. **For more information on our vendors,** click **here**.  

**(c) Information Third Parties Provide About You**  

We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect directly from you on our Service with outside records from third parties for various purposes, including to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities that may be of interest to you.  To the extent we combine information we receive from those sources with your Personal Information we collect on the Service, it will be treated as Personal Information and we will apply this Privacy Policy to such combined information, unless we have disclosed otherwise. In no other circumstances do our statements under this Privacy Policy apply to information we receive about you from third parties.  

**(d)**   **Interactions with Third-Party Services**  

The Service may include functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between the Service and a third-party web site or application.  The use of this functionality may involve the third-party operator providing certain information, including Personal Information, to us.  For example, when you apply for a job with us, you may have an option to use your LinkedIn or other account provided by a third-party site or application to facilitate that process on the Service, or otherwise link accounts.  If we offer and you choose to use this functionality, the third-party site or application may send Personal Information about you to us.  If so, we will then treat it as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy, since we are collecting it as a result of your accessing of and interaction on our Service. Further, when you use third-party sites or services, you are using their services and not our services and they, not we, are responsible for their practices.  You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party tools on our Service.   

**Return to policy summary and navigation**
